{
    "subject": "resource/John_Doyle_(RAF_officer)",
    "predicate": "ontology/deathDate",
    "object": "1974-11-24",
    "human_readable": "John Doyle (RAF officer) died on November 24, 1974.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.7533981204032898,
            "question": "When did John Doyle die?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7158498764038086,
            "question": "What was John Doyle's role in the RAF?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.672971248626709,
            "question": "Was John Doyle a military officer?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5200105309486389,
            "question": "Were there any notable events during John Doyle's service in the RAF?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4581294059753418,
            "question": "What was John Doyle's profession?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.45281994342803955,
            "question": "Do any details about John Doyle's life prior to his death exist?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4276476502418518,
            "question": "In which organization did John Doyle serve?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.41961854696273804,
            "question": "On what date did John Doyle pass away?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3034840524196625,
            "question": "Is there any information available about John Doyle's family or personal life?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2960127294063568,
            "question": "What is known about John Doyle's legacy or impact?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=John Doyle (RAF officer) died on November 24, 1974.",
            "html": "dbpedia_1847_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is there any information available about John Doyle's family or personal life?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1847_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=On what date did John Doyle pass away?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1847_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=In which organization did John Doyle serve?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1847_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1847_106.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1847_109.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1847_123.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1847_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1847_42.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1847_57.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1847_65.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1847_80.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1847_87.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1847_9.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nExplanation: The document for `57.txt` contains the information about John Edgcumbe Doyle DFC, who was a British World War I pilot and mentions his death date as \"24 November 1974.\" This supports the statement that John Doyle (RAF officer) died on November 24, 1974."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n    \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}